{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953802518","data":{"timestamp":" 946953802517"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953843025","data":{"timestamp":" 946953843025"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953868687","data":{"timestamp":" 946953868687"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953894388","data":{"timestamp":" 946953894388"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953923795","data":{"timestamp":" 946953923795"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953955757","data":{"timestamp":" 946953955757"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953984982","data":{"timestamp":" 946953984982"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954016914","data":{"timestamp":" 946954016914"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954047797","data":{"timestamp":" 946954047797"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954047859","data":{"timestamp":" 946954047859"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" a783c649-dbd3-4165-878d-8904a046eaf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954062519","data":{"timestamp":" 946954062518"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954067551","data":{"timestamp":" 946954067551"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954069130","data":{"timestamp":" 946954069130"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954072314","data":{"timestamp":" 946954072314"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954074234","data":{"timestamp":" 946954074233"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954075819","data":{"timestamp":" 946954075819"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954083499","data":{"timestamp":" 946954083499"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954085080","data":{"timestamp":" 946954085079"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954089592","data":{"timestamp":" 946954089592"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954091166","data":{"timestamp":" 946954091165"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954101115","data":{"timestamp":" 946954101115"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954102727","data":{"timestamp":" 946954102724"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954110647","data":{"timestamp":" 946954110646"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954112263","data":{"timestamp":" 946954112263"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954119018","data":{"timestamp":" 946954119018"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954120608","data":{"timestamp":" 946954120608"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954127432","data":{"timestamp":" 946954127432"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954129029","data":{"timestamp":" 946954129029"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954137158","data":{"timestamp":" 946954137157"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954139664","data":{"timestamp":" 946954139664"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954142274","data":{"timestamp":" 946954142274"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954143880","data":{"timestamp":" 946954143880"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954146370","data":{"timestamp":" 946954146369"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954147971","data":{"timestamp":" 946954147970"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954150528","data":{"timestamp":" 946954150527"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954152550","data":{"timestamp":" 946954152549"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954152656","data":{"timestamp":" 946954152656"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954165110","data":{"timestamp":" 946954165110"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ce86cdbe-a723-4a5c-a90f-98b40ee24cd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-people.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954174513","data":{"timestamp":" 946954174512"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954179417","data":{"timestamp":" 946954179417"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954191123","data":{"timestamp":" 946954191122"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954191132","data":{"timestamp":" 946954191132"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954191534","data":{"timestamp":" 946954191534"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954196535","data":{"timestamp":" 946954196534"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954198738","data":{"timestamp":" 946954198738"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954198812","data":{"timestamp":" 946954198811"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954215865","data":{"timestamp":" 946954215864"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 946c7cc9-30be-4c35-8f98-da86e3bf0d09"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954215921","data":{"timestamp":" 946954215921"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" f2a21de5-ac8d-4b3a-a3e9-469ec678e523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956609937","data":{"timestamp":" 946956609937"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_kaka-baba-mama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956615634","data":{"timestamp":" 946956615634"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mkulima-kinyozi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956620583","data":{"timestamp":" 946956620583"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_dada-kinyozi-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956626170","data":{"timestamp":" 946956626170"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_bibi-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956631775","data":{"timestamp":" 946956631774"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_mkulima-mwanafunzi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956636397","data":{"timestamp":" 946956636397"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_mwalimu-kinyozi-babu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956641219","data":{"timestamp":" 946956641219"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shangazi_shangazi-bibi-dada"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shangazi"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956645959","data":{"timestamp":" 946956645958"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956651859","data":{"timestamp":" 946956651859"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_kinyozi-mwanafunzi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956657020","data":{"timestamp":" 946956657020"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956663784","data":{"timestamp":" 946956663783"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956669540","data":{"timestamp":" 946956669539"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4ce563fc-876d-4625-bf9c-08892c8f2574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956684954","data":{"timestamp":" 946956684954"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956690932","data":{"timestamp":" 946956690932"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956695666","data":{"timestamp":" 946956695666"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956700971","data":{"timestamp":" 946956700970"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956706916","data":{"timestamp":" 946956706916"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956711312","data":{"timestamp":" 946956711312"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956715768","data":{"timestamp":" 946956715768"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956720190","data":{"timestamp":" 946956720190"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956724897","data":{"timestamp":" 946956724897"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956731914","data":{"timestamp":" 946956731914"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956738467","data":{"timestamp":" 946956738465"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956746514","data":{"timestamp":" 946956746514"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" ba210e6d-6d44-45d5-ad74-b7c9ee4cfade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956794572","data":{"timestamp":" 946956794572"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_yule-kuku-kubwa-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956842345","data":{"timestamp":" 946956842344"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kucha-msimu-i-kuzaliwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" kucha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956867769","data":{"timestamp":" 946956867769"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_wapi-kwanza-mwingine-usiku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" usiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956932114","data":{"timestamp":" 946956932113"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" usiku_wapi-kwanza-mwingine-usiku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956932256","data":{"timestamp":" 946956932256"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956943671","data":{"timestamp":" 946956943670"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 459b2bb3-e1ce-45d0-b704-ac08498a5732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956974995","data":{"timestamp":" 946956974995"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956979187","data":{"timestamp":" 946956979187"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956983438","data":{"timestamp":" 946956983438"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956987714","data":{"timestamp":" 946956987714"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956988890","data":{"timestamp":" 946956988890"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956994620","data":{"timestamp":" 946956994619"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957000039","data":{"timestamp":" 946957000039"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957004978","data":{"timestamp":" 946957004978"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957009750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957009750"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957013917","data":{"timestamp":" 946957013917"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957015824","data":{"timestamp":" 946957015823"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957020470","data":{"timestamp":" 946957020470"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957024569","data":{"timestamp":" 946957024569"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957026334","data":{"timestamp":" 946957026333"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957028305","data":{"timestamp":" 946957028304"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957035651","data":{"timestamp":" 946957035651"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957045397","data":{"timestamp":" 946957045397"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957052631","data":{"timestamp":" 946957052631"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6afb29b5-bcdd-46c3-b267-cf3f39903134"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957065352","data":{"timestamp":" 946957065352"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 116652a6-f5b7-4779-a305-0d8e30a3245d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957070531","data":{"timestamp":" 946957070531"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 116652a6-f5b7-4779-a305-0d8e30a3245d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957076136","data":{"timestamp":" 946957076136"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 116652a6-f5b7-4779-a305-0d8e30a3245d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957081663","data":{"timestamp":" 946957081663"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 116652a6-f5b7-4779-a305-0d8e30a3245d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957082859","data":{"timestamp":" 946957082859"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 116652a6-f5b7-4779-a305-0d8e30a3245d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957098641","data":{"timestamp":" 946957098641"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957103321","data":{"timestamp":" 946957103321"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957109118","data":{"timestamp":" 946957109118"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957114052","data":{"timestamp":" 946957114052"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957118724","data":{"timestamp":" 946957118724"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957124766","data":{"timestamp":" 946957124765"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957129069","data":{"timestamp":" 946957129069"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_baba-watoto-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957133884","data":{"timestamp":" 946957133884"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" bibi_bibi-mjoma-wakulima-babu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957137623","data":{"timestamp":" 946957137623"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_baba-wakulima-mama-kaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957150286","data":{"timestamp":" 946957150285"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957152269","data":{"timestamp":" 946957152267"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" de754a17-8e10-4e8b-8cd8-72523b9e42b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957161894","data":{"timestamp":" 946957161894"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957162593","data":{"timestamp":" 946957162592"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957163571","data":{"timestamp":" 946957163570"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957163773","data":{"timestamp":" 946957163772"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957164384","data":{"timestamp":" 946957164383"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957165139","data":{"timestamp":" 946957165138"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957165573","data":{"timestamp":" 946957165573"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957166167","data":{"timestamp":" 946957166167"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957169703","data":{"timestamp":" 946957169703"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATUMA"," userResponse":" ALIWATUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957170304","data":{"timestamp":" 946957170304"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957170714","data":{"timestamp":" 946957170714"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957171312","data":{"timestamp":" 946957171312"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957171391","data":{"timestamp":" 946957171391"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957176984","data":{"timestamp":" 946957176984"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957182177","data":{"timestamp":" 946957182177"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957187001","data":{"timestamp":" 946957187001"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" fb9aa854-f82f-4139-aa86-2110330ea89d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957198092","data":{"timestamp":" 946957198091"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957198275","data":{"timestamp":" 946957198275"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957198605","data":{"timestamp":" 946957198605"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957199767","data":{"timestamp":" 946957199766"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957200490","data":{"timestamp":" 946957200490"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957203695","data":{"timestamp":" 946957203695"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957204335","data":{"timestamp":" 946957204335"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957205128","data":{"timestamp":" 946957205127"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957205980","data":{"timestamp":" 946957205979"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957206902","data":{"timestamp":" 946957206902"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957207595","data":{"timestamp":" 946957207595"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957210567","data":{"timestamp":" 946957210566"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957211278","data":{"timestamp":" 946957211277"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957212302","data":{"timestamp":" 946957212302"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957212484","data":{"timestamp":" 946957212483"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957213246","data":{"timestamp":" 946957213246"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957216333","data":{"timestamp":" 946957216332"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957217167","data":{"timestamp":" 946957217167"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957217233","data":{"timestamp":" 946957217233"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957217823","data":{"timestamp":" 946957217823"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957218405","data":{"timestamp":" 946957218404"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957219202","data":{"timestamp":" 946957219201"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957222685","data":{"timestamp":" 946957222684"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957223315","data":{"timestamp":" 946957223315"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957223987","data":{"timestamp":" 946957223986"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957226978","data":{"timestamp":" 946957226978"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957227875","data":{"timestamp":" 946957227875"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957228977","data":{"timestamp":" 946957228977"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957230154","data":{"timestamp":" 946957230154"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957233516","data":{"timestamp":" 946957233515"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957233906","data":{"timestamp":" 946957233906"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957234530","data":{"timestamp":" 946957234529"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957235744","data":{"timestamp":" 946957235743"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957236397","data":{"timestamp":" 946957236397"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957237850","data":{"timestamp":" 946957237850"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957238706","data":{"timestamp":" 946957238706"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957241774","data":{"timestamp":" 946957241774"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957242747","data":{"timestamp":" 946957242747"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957243619","data":{"timestamp":" 946957243619"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957244287","data":{"timestamp":" 946957244287"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957245322","data":{"timestamp":" 946957245321"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957246604","data":{"timestamp":" 946957246603"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957246649","data":{"timestamp":" 946957246649"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957247528","data":{"timestamp":" 946957247528"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957248630","data":{"timestamp":" 946957248629"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957250982","data":{"timestamp":" 946957250981"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957251738","data":{"timestamp":" 946957251738"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957252598","data":{"timestamp":" 946957252598"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957254716","data":{"timestamp":" 946957254716"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957255279","data":{"timestamp":" 946957255279"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957256070","data":{"timestamp":" 946957256070"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957256592","data":{"timestamp":" 946957256592"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957257400","data":{"timestamp":" 946957257399"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957258086","data":{"timestamp":" 946957258086"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957258945","data":{"timestamp":" 946957258945"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957261797","data":{"timestamp":" 946957261797"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957262604","data":{"timestamp":" 946957262603"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957264189","data":{"timestamp":" 946957264189"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957264422","data":{"timestamp":" 946957264422"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957264972","data":{"timestamp":" 946957264970"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957265779","data":{"timestamp":" 946957265778"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957266394","data":{"timestamp":" 946957266393"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957267452","data":{"timestamp":" 946957267450"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957267957","data":{"timestamp":" 946957267943"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957270338","data":{"timestamp":" 946957270338"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957270763","data":{"timestamp":" 946957270762"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957271314","data":{"timestamp":" 946957271313"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957272683","data":{"timestamp":" 946957272683"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957276140","data":{"timestamp":" 946957276139"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957277081","data":{"timestamp":" 946957277081"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957277812","data":{"timestamp":" 946957277811"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957278046","data":{"timestamp":" 946957278045"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957278643","data":{"timestamp":" 946957278642"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957279497","data":{"timestamp":" 946957279497"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957279682","data":{"timestamp":" 946957279681"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957280306","data":{"timestamp":" 946957280305"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957282146","data":{"timestamp":" 946957282145"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957282932","data":{"timestamp":" 946957282931"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957285906","data":{"timestamp":" 946957285906"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957286728","data":{"timestamp":" 946957286728"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957287389","data":{"timestamp":" 946957287388"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957288002","data":{"timestamp":" 946957288002"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957288395","data":{"timestamp":" 946957288394"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957288592","data":{"timestamp":" 946957288592"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957289328","data":{"timestamp":" 946957289328"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957292278","data":{"timestamp":" 946957292277"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957292938","data":{"timestamp":" 946957292938"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957293779","data":{"timestamp":" 946957293778"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957294479","data":{"timestamp":" 946957294478"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957295275","data":{"timestamp":" 946957295275"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957297900","data":{"timestamp":" 946957297899"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957299090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957299090"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957299884","data":{"timestamp":" 946957299884"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957300673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957300671"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957303604","data":{"timestamp":" 946957303602"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957305982","data":{"timestamp":" 946957305982"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306007","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306007"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306033","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306033"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306047","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306047"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306070","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306070"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306089"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306963","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306963"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957307843","data":{"timestamp":" 946957307842"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957310644","data":{"timestamp":" 946957310644"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957311138","data":{"timestamp":" 946957311138"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957311890","data":{"timestamp":" 946957311890"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957312967","data":{"timestamp":" 946957312967"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957313383","data":{"timestamp":" 946957313382"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957314093","data":{"timestamp":" 946957314093"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957317214","data":{"timestamp":" 946957317213"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957318174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957318173"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957318916","data":{"timestamp":" 946957318915"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957319579","data":{"timestamp":" 946957319578"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957320485","data":{"timestamp":" 946957320485"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957323183","data":{"timestamp":" 946957323183"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957323998","data":{"timestamp":" 946957323997"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957324819","data":{"timestamp":" 946957324819"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957327387","data":{"timestamp":" 946957327387"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957328014","data":{"timestamp":" 946957328013"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957328597","data":{"timestamp":" 946957328597"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957329577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957329576"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957330490","data":{"timestamp":" 946957330490"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957331546","data":{"timestamp":" 946957331546"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957332121","data":{"timestamp":" 946957332121"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957334807","data":{"timestamp":" 946957334806"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957334909","data":{"timestamp":" 946957334909"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957370116","data":{"timestamp":" 946957370115"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957380031","data":{"timestamp":" 946957380031"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957385994","data":{"timestamp":" 946957385994"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 80766e14-3be6-4381-8850-190c7aa90ec1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957396281","data":{"timestamp":" 946957396280"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957398685","data":{"timestamp":" 946957398684"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957399131","data":{"timestamp":" 946957399131"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957399329","data":{"timestamp":" 946957399329"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957399839","data":{"timestamp":" 946957399838"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957402782","data":{"timestamp":" 946957402780"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957403378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957403378"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957403562","data":{"timestamp":" 946957403562"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957404324","data":{"timestamp":" 946957404324"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957406976","data":{"timestamp":" 946957406975"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957407758","data":{"timestamp":" 946957407757"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957410777","data":{"timestamp":" 946957410777"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957412007","data":{"timestamp":" 946957412006"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957412448","data":{"timestamp":" 946957412447"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957413207","data":{"timestamp":" 946957413206"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957415792","data":{"timestamp":" 946957415792"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957417266","data":{"timestamp":" 946957417266"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957417715","data":{"timestamp":" 946957417714"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957420142","data":{"timestamp":" 946957420142"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957420502","data":{"timestamp":" 946957420502"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957421466","data":{"timestamp":" 946957421466"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957421959","data":{"timestamp":" 946957421959"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957422877","data":{"timestamp":" 946957422877"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957425770","data":{"timestamp":" 946957425767"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957426649","data":{"timestamp":" 946957426648"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957427312","data":{"timestamp":" 946957427311"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957428396","data":{"timestamp":" 946957428395"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957431675","data":{"timestamp":" 946957431675"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957432165","data":{"timestamp":" 946957432164"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957432782","data":{"timestamp":" 946957432782"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957433353","data":{"timestamp":" 946957433353"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957434679","data":{"timestamp":" 946957434679"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957435075","data":{"timestamp":" 946957435074"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957435786","data":{"timestamp":" 946957435786"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957438359","data":{"timestamp":" 946957438359"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957439162","data":{"timestamp":" 946957439161"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957439788","data":{"timestamp":" 946957439787"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957440131","data":{"timestamp":" 946957440130"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957443618","data":{"timestamp":" 946957443618"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957444309","data":{"timestamp":" 946957444309"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957445434","data":{"timestamp":" 946957445434"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957446199","data":{"timestamp":" 946957446198"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957446752","data":{"timestamp":" 946957446748"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957450200","data":{"timestamp":" 946957450200"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957453118","data":{"timestamp":" 946957453118"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957453901","data":{"timestamp":" 946957453901"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957454824","data":{"timestamp":" 946957454824"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957455641","data":{"timestamp":" 946957455641"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957456145","data":{"timestamp":" 946957456144"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957456436","data":{"timestamp":" 946957456435"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957457582","data":{"timestamp":" 946957457581"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957460341","data":{"timestamp":" 946957460341"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957460675","data":{"timestamp":" 946957460674"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" YAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957460938","data":{"timestamp":" 946957460938"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957461938","data":{"timestamp":" 946957461938"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957465390","data":{"timestamp":" 946957465390"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957466241","data":{"timestamp":" 946957466241"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPITA"," userResponse":" ANAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957467236","data":{"timestamp":" 946957467235"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957469623","data":{"timestamp":" 946957469623"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957470495","data":{"timestamp":" 946957470495"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHIFU"," userResponse":" NADHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957471298","data":{"timestamp":" 946957471298"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957473844","data":{"timestamp":" 946957473844"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957474302","data":{"timestamp":" 946957474302"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957474577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957474577"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957475236","data":{"timestamp":" 946957475236"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957475685","data":{"timestamp":" 946957475685"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957478358","data":{"timestamp":" 946957478358"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINAENDA"," userResponse":" VINAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957479343","data":{"timestamp":" 946957479342"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957479870","data":{"timestamp":" 946957479870"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957480340","data":{"timestamp":" 946957480340"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957482942","data":{"timestamp":" 946957482941"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957483402","data":{"timestamp":" 946957483402"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957483795","data":{"timestamp":" 946957483795"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957487060","data":{"timestamp":" 946957487059"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," userResponse":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957490358","data":{"timestamp":" 946957490358"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957491000","data":{"timestamp":" 946957490999"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957491962","data":{"timestamp":" 946957491961"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957492780","data":{"timestamp":" 946957492773"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957493538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957493538"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957496266","data":{"timestamp":" 946957496266"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" NAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957497129","data":{"timestamp":" 946957497128"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957498020","data":{"timestamp":" 946957498020"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957500351","data":{"timestamp":" 946957500351"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957501173","data":{"timestamp":" 946957501172"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957501463","data":{"timestamp":" 946957501463"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957502307","data":{"timestamp":" 946957502307"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957503141","data":{"timestamp":" 946957503141"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957505334","data":{"timestamp":" 946957505333"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957506872","data":{"timestamp":" 946957506871"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVIPENDA"," userResponse":" UNAVIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957510092","data":{"timestamp":" 946957510092"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957512590","data":{"timestamp":" 946957512589"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957513577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957513576"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957514604","data":{"timestamp":" 946957514602"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPELEKA"," userResponse":" WANAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957515213","data":{"timestamp":" 946957515213"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957515813","data":{"timestamp":" 946957515812"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAO"," userResponse":" CHAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957516065","data":{"timestamp":" 946957516064"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957516961","data":{"timestamp":" 946957516960"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957518105","data":{"timestamp":" 946957518105"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957518918","data":{"timestamp":" 946957518917"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWANI"," userResponse":" VICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957519476","data":{"timestamp":" 946957519476"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAO"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957521376","data":{"timestamp":" 946957521376"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957522027","data":{"timestamp":" 946957522027"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957522780","data":{"timestamp":" 946957522779"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEREVU"," userResponse":" WEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957526122","data":{"timestamp":" 946957526122"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957526845","data":{"timestamp":" 946957526844"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957527859","data":{"timestamp":" 946957527859"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUKWA"," userResponse":" ANASUKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957528255","data":{"timestamp":" 946957528255"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957528798","data":{"timestamp":" 946957528797"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957531648","data":{"timestamp":" 946957531647"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDA"," userResponse":" ATAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957532179","data":{"timestamp":" 946957532179"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957532416","data":{"timestamp":" 946957532416"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957533211","data":{"timestamp":" 946957533211"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957533798","data":{"timestamp":" 946957533798"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957534563","data":{"timestamp":" 946957534562"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535196","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535196"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957538401","data":{"timestamp":" 946957538401"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMECHOKA"," userResponse":" NIMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957539027","data":{"timestamp":" 946957539027"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957541794","data":{"timestamp":" 946957541793"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957542750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957542750"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIWEKA"," userResponse":" ANANIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957543560","data":{"timestamp":" 946957543560"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957544133","data":{"timestamp":" 946957544132"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957545837","data":{"timestamp":" 946957545836"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," userResponse":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957548970","data":{"timestamp":" 946957548970"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957550237","data":{"timestamp":" 946957550237"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957550670","data":{"timestamp":" 946957550669"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957551496","data":{"timestamp":" 946957551496"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957553119","data":{"timestamp":" 946957553119"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USICHELEWE"," userResponse":" USICHELEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957554141","data":{"timestamp":" 946957554141"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957555212","data":{"timestamp":" 946957555212"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957555704","data":{"timestamp":" 946957555704"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957556211","data":{"timestamp":" 946957556211"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGO"," userResponse":" LANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957557160","data":{"timestamp":" 946957557159"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957559935","data":{"timestamp":" 946957559935"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957560588","data":{"timestamp":" 946957560588"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957561181","data":{"timestamp":" 946957561181"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957561433","data":{"timestamp":" 946957561433"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMI"," userResponse":" TUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957564472","data":{"timestamp":" 946957564472"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957564798","data":{"timestamp":" 946957564798"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957565787","data":{"timestamp":" 946957565787"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" ANAPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957568471","data":{"timestamp":" 946957568471"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957569220","data":{"timestamp":" 946957569220"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957569673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957569672"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957570462","data":{"timestamp":" 946957570462"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957573573","data":{"timestamp":" 946957573573"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957573943","data":{"timestamp":" 946957573943"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957574768","data":{"timestamp":" 946957574767"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957575697","data":{"timestamp":" 946957575696"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUKA"," userResponse":" WANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957576638","data":{"timestamp":" 946957576637"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957577462","data":{"timestamp":" 946957577462"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957580416","data":{"timestamp":" 946957580415"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957581078","data":{"timestamp":" 946957581077"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFIKE"," userResponse":" WAFIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957581918","data":{"timestamp":" 946957581918"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957582583","data":{"timestamp":" 946957582583"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957583034","data":{"timestamp":" 946957583034"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957583843","data":{"timestamp":" 946957583842"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957587037","data":{"timestamp":" 946957587037"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957587572","data":{"timestamp":" 946957587571"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957588165","data":{"timestamp":" 946957588165"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957588827","data":{"timestamp":" 946957588827"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957590197","data":{"timestamp":" 946957590197"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957592844","data":{"timestamp":" 946957592843"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957594132","data":{"timestamp":" 946957594131"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALIVINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957595128","data":{"timestamp":" 946957595127"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957595475","data":{"timestamp":" 946957595475"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957597840","data":{"timestamp":" 946957597839"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957598536","data":{"timestamp":" 946957598536"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957599718","data":{"timestamp":" 946957599718"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITANUNUA"," userResponse":" NITANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957600364","data":{"timestamp":" 946957600364"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957601196","data":{"timestamp":" 946957601195"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957602076","data":{"timestamp":" 946957602076"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYANGU"," userResponse":" VYANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957602384","data":{"timestamp":" 946957602383"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957602647","data":{"timestamp":" 946957602646"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957603370","data":{"timestamp":" 946957603370"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957606625","data":{"timestamp":" 946957606624"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957607472","data":{"timestamp":" 946957607472"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANZA"," userResponse":" ANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957608174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957608173"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOKA"," userResponse":" KUCHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957608791","data":{"timestamp":" 946957608791"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957612012","data":{"timestamp":" 946957612012"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" NAMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957612559","data":{"timestamp":" 946957612558"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957613666","data":{"timestamp":" 946957613666"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957614135","data":{"timestamp":" 946957614135"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957615071","data":{"timestamp":" 946957615070"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957616495","data":{"timestamp":" 946957616494"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUJA"," userResponse":" UNAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957618331","data":{"timestamp":" 946957618330"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUNASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957618913","data":{"timestamp":" 946957618913"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957619141","data":{"timestamp":" 946957619141"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957620090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957620089"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957623104","data":{"timestamp":" 946957623104"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOJA"," userResponse":" NGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957626378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957626377"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASIKIA"," userResponse":" NINASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957626936","data":{"timestamp":" 946957626936"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957629594","data":{"timestamp":" 946957629594"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957630197","data":{"timestamp":" 946957630197"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957631217","data":{"timestamp":" 946957631216"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957634208","data":{"timestamp":" 946957634208"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957634417","data":{"timestamp":" 946957634416"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957635018","data":{"timestamp":" 946957635018"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957635253","data":{"timestamp":" 946957635252"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957635904","data":{"timestamp":" 946957635903"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957636700","data":{"timestamp":" 946957636700"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957639609","data":{"timestamp":" 946957639608"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEKUJA"," userResponse":" IMEKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957640688","data":{"timestamp":" 946957640688"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUNIPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957641461","data":{"timestamp":" 946957641460"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957641673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957641673"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957642476","data":{"timestamp":" 946957642476"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957643391","data":{"timestamp":" 946957643391"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957647136","data":{"timestamp":" 946957647136"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" NIMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957648393","data":{"timestamp":" 946957648393"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957652516","data":{"timestamp":" 946957652516"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655279","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655278"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655383","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655382"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" be924539-08a9-4d68-92f2-55d905b111d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957669190","data":{"timestamp":" 946957669190"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mkono_mkono-kichwa-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957674098","data":{"timestamp":" 946957674098"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" ndevu_sikio-tumbo-ndevu-pua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndevu"," userResponse":" ndevu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957678630","data":{"timestamp":" 946957678629"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_kichwa-mkono-sikio-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957684774","data":{"timestamp":" 946957684774"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_ndevu-ngumi-kichwa-mkono"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957688512","data":{"timestamp":" 946957688512"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_tumbo-mikono-nywele-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957693296","data":{"timestamp":" 946957693296"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nyayo_nywele-vidole-pua-nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyayo"," userResponse":" nyayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957698280","data":{"timestamp":" 946957698280"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mdomo_mkono-nywele-mdomo-bega"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdomo"," userResponse":" mdomo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957702457","data":{"timestamp":" 946957702457"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_vidole-meno-sikio-pua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957707837","data":{"timestamp":" 946957707837"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mguu_meno-mguu-goti-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957712594","data":{"timestamp":" 946957712594"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_goti-sikio-pua-meno"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957714561","data":{"timestamp":" 946957714558"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6760a1b7-ad22-48d1-9cb2-29689b216d2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" meno_goti-sikio-pua-meno"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957728345","data":{"timestamp":" 946957728345"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_mguu-meno-goti-kichwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957731421","data":{"timestamp":" 946957731421"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_vidole-meno-sikio-pua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957734860","data":{"timestamp":" 946957734860"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mguu_meno-mguu-goti-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957739591","data":{"timestamp":" 946957739591"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mikono_mikono-mguu-pua-nywele"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mikono"," userResponse":" mikono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742987","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742987"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_kichwa-mkono-sikio-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957746442","data":{"timestamp":" 946957746441"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" jicho_jicho-mkono-vidole-sikio"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957750165","data":{"timestamp":" 946957750165"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" goti_pua-goti-ndevu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957754015","data":{"timestamp":" 946957754014"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_goti-sikio-pua-meno"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957757487","data":{"timestamp":" 946957757487"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_tumbo-nywele-ndevu-vidole"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957761076","data":{"timestamp":" 946957761076"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mdomo_mkono-nywele-mdomo-bega"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdomo"," userResponse":" mdomo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957763062","data":{"timestamp":" 946957763061"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mdomo_mkono-nywele-mdomo-bega"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957773893","data":{"timestamp":" 946957773892"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" abb44b5b-3933-43be-9610-0435e8a5191f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mdomo_mkono-nywele-mdomo-bega"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957800514","data":{"timestamp":" 946957800513"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957801522","data":{"timestamp":" 946957801522"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957804459","data":{"timestamp":" 946957804459"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zeze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957805136","data":{"timestamp":" 946957805136"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zeze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957808198","data":{"timestamp":" 946957808198"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kichwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" chwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957809412","data":{"timestamp":" 946957809412"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kichwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957810264","data":{"timestamp":" 946957810264"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kichwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chwa"," userResponse":" chwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957813661","data":{"timestamp":" 946957813661"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957814071","data":{"timestamp":" 946957814071"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957818270","data":{"timestamp":" 946957818270"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957820354","data":{"timestamp":" 946957820354"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825018","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825018"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825317","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825317"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957828916","data":{"timestamp":" 946957828916"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957829226","data":{"timestamp":" 946957829226"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957832976","data":{"timestamp":" 946957832976"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957833370","data":{"timestamp":" 946957833370"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834085","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834084"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957837238","data":{"timestamp":" 946957837238"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957837488","data":{"timestamp":" 946957837488"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842415","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842415"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842708","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842708"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957845787","data":{"timestamp":" 946957845787"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957854673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957854672"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957870122","data":{"timestamp":" 946957870121"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957877983","data":{"timestamp":" 946957877982"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 68c62a0f-7373-4640-a3c4-0c2960206c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957890408","data":{"timestamp":" 946957890407"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957890717","data":{"timestamp":" 946957890717"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yo"," userResponse":" yo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957894174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957894174"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957894499","data":{"timestamp":" 946957894499"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957897795","data":{"timestamp":" 946957897795"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957898644","data":{"timestamp":" 946957898644"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957899055","data":{"timestamp":" 946957899055"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957903218","data":{"timestamp":" 946957903217"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957904284","data":{"timestamp":" 946957904283"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957907807","data":{"timestamp":" 946957907806"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957908134","data":{"timestamp":" 946957908134"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957911541","data":{"timestamp":" 946957911541"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957911798","data":{"timestamp":" 946957911798"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957915640","data":{"timestamp":" 946957915639"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hema"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957915925","data":{"timestamp":" 946957915925"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hema"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957922902","data":{"timestamp":" 946957922902"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957929148","data":{"timestamp":" 946957929147"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957930165","data":{"timestamp":" 946957930165"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957933756","data":{"timestamp":" 946957933756"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957935380","data":{"timestamp":" 946957935380"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957939362","data":{"timestamp":" 946957939362"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957939738","data":{"timestamp":" 946957939738"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957942063","data":{"timestamp":" 946957942062"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957950709","data":{"timestamp":" 946957950708"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957958863","data":{"timestamp":" 946957958863"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957965504","data":{"timestamp":" 946957965504"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957971954","data":{"timestamp":" 946957971953"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957979175","data":{"timestamp":" 946957979174"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6977dfec-561e-4db7-b9ee-1a5a8efda2f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_bata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957994140","data":{"timestamp":" 946957994140"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957994415","data":{"timestamp":" 946957994415"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957999030","data":{"timestamp":" 946957999030"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958004855","data":{"timestamp":" 946958004855"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958010858","data":{"timestamp":" 946958010858"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958017458","data":{"timestamp":" 946958017458"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 493e42c6-fba5-496d-ac92-de03a787250e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958030003","data":{"timestamp":" 946958030003"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958030588","data":{"timestamp":" 946958030588"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958031505","data":{"timestamp":" 946958031504"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958031652","data":{"timestamp":" 946958031652"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958032368","data":{"timestamp":" 946958032368"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958033066","data":{"timestamp":" 946958033066"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958033794","data":{"timestamp":" 946958033794"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958034393","data":{"timestamp":" 946958034392"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958034621","data":{"timestamp":" 946958034621"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958035110","data":{"timestamp":" 946958035109"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958049896","data":{"timestamp":" 946958049896"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958050996","data":{"timestamp":" 946958050996"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958052914","data":{"timestamp":" 946958052914"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958054740","data":{"timestamp":" 946958054740"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958055327","data":{"timestamp":" 946958055326"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958055510","data":{"timestamp":" 946958055510"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958061238","data":{"timestamp":" 946958061238"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958074597","data":{"timestamp":" 946958074596"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958079834","data":{"timestamp":" 946958079834"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 41de74e6-bbac-4c03-9a40-c14b328da3a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958092167","data":{"timestamp":" 946958092167"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958092775","data":{"timestamp":" 946958092775"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958093700","data":{"timestamp":" 946958093699"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958093843","data":{"timestamp":" 946958093843"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958094573","data":{"timestamp":" 946958094573"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958095282","data":{"timestamp":" 946958095281"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958096000","data":{"timestamp":" 946958096000"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958096579","data":{"timestamp":" 946958096579"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958096812","data":{"timestamp":" 946958096812"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958097312","data":{"timestamp":" 946958097311"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958100697","data":{"timestamp":" 946958100697"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958100867","data":{"timestamp":" 946958100867"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958105860","data":{"timestamp":" 946958105860"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958112107","data":{"timestamp":" 946958112107"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958117396","data":{"timestamp":" 946958117395"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 6d24f669-736c-435e-a5d3-9923d0c3bf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958130069","data":{"timestamp":" 946958130069"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958130678","data":{"timestamp":" 946958130678"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958131608","data":{"timestamp":" 946958131608"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958131752","data":{"timestamp":" 946958131752"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958132470","data":{"timestamp":" 946958132470"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958133154","data":{"timestamp":" 946958133154"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958133889","data":{"timestamp":" 946958133889"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958134464","data":{"timestamp":" 946958134464"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958134694","data":{"timestamp":" 946958134694"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958135186","data":{"timestamp":" 946958135186"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958139069","data":{"timestamp":" 946958139069"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958140236","data":{"timestamp":" 946958140236"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958142044","data":{"timestamp":" 946958142044"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958143976","data":{"timestamp":" 946958143976"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958145943","data":{"timestamp":" 946958145942"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958148134","data":{"timestamp":" 946958148134"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958150042","data":{"timestamp":" 946958150042"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958152251","data":{"timestamp":" 946958152250"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958154809","data":{"timestamp":" 946958154809"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958157274","data":{"timestamp":" 946958157274"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958160105","data":{"timestamp":" 946958160105"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958160619","data":{"timestamp":" 946958160619"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958161222","data":{"timestamp":" 946958161222"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958162026","data":{"timestamp":" 946958162025"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958162919","data":{"timestamp":" 946958162919"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958166341","data":{"timestamp":" 946958166341"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958168255","data":{"timestamp":" 946958168254"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958169942","data":{"timestamp":" 946958169941"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958171954","data":{"timestamp":" 946958171953"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958173967","data":{"timestamp":" 946958173966"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958175632","data":{"timestamp":" 946958175632"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958176212","data":{"timestamp":" 946958176212"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958176644","data":{"timestamp":" 946958176644"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958176759","data":{"timestamp":" 946958176759"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958177185","data":{"timestamp":" 946958177184"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958177299","data":{"timestamp":" 946958177299"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958177342","data":{"timestamp":" 946958177342"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958177740","data":{"timestamp":" 946958177739"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958182734","data":{"timestamp":" 946958182734"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958182845","data":{"timestamp":" 946958182845"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20000104_054311"," gameId":" 4b4985ed-ca33-4ebc-8fca-60627d233301"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}